[
 {
  "Question": "My brother works in a factory.",
  "A": "Assertive",
  "B": " Interrogative",
  "C": " Imperative",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Assertive"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Why are you so weak?",
  "A": "Imperative",
  "B": "Interrogative",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Interrogative"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Are you going to Hyderabad now?",
  "A": "Imperative",
  "B": "Imperative",
  "C": "Exclamatory",
  "D": "Interrogative",
  "Answer": "Interrogative"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Laxmi is my best friend",
  "A": "InterrogativeInterrog",
  "B": "Imperative",
  "C": "Assertive",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Assertive"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Suvarsha is in class IL.",
  "A": "Exclamatory",
  "B": "Interrogative",
  "C": "Assertive",
  "D": "Imperative",
  "Answer": "Assertive"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Get out.",
  "A": "Exclamatory",
  "B": "Assertive",
  "C": "Assertive",
  "D": "Imperative",
  "Answer": "Imperative"
 },
 {
  "Question": "May I come in please?",
  "A": "Interrogative",
  "B": "Assertive",
  "C": "Imperative",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Interrogative"
 },
 {
  "Question": "Ramesh does not go to office.",
  "A": "Imperative",
  "B": "Interrogative",
  "C": "Assertive",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Imperative"
 },
 {
  "Question": "What a beautiful statue it is!",
  "A": "Assertive",
  "B": "Imperative",
  "C": "Interrogative",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Exclamatory"
 },
 {
  "Question": "How many boys are there in the class ?",
  "A": "Interrogative",
  "B": "Assertive",
  "C": "Imperative",
  "D": "Exclamatory",
  "Answer": "Interrogative"
 }
]
